But now, if this is how it is, I wish
you'd kept on being a jerk to me!
If you had, I wouldn't have
realized how I felt about you!
I wouldn't have felt sad and
jealous when I found out about her!
And I wouldn't have tried forgetting about
you and FALLING IN LOVE
WITH Kirito instead!
I'm sorry.
Go on.
Leave me alone.
Emily 20 21 21 22 23
28 29 In fact that I'm on the path.
I'm not gonna be gone.
I'm not going to be in the dark.
I'm not going to be here.
I can't see the future.
But I'm trying to scream.
I'm trying to cry.
I'm trying to make a certain way.
I'm trying to make a little more.
I'm trying to go to the sky.
From above.
From next stage.
From east.
I remember the day when
everything changed.
The day I found out I wasn't
really part of this family.
It felt weird.
Like I didn't fit in with them anymore.
And I found this out.
when I was 10.
I'd wonder, who is she?
And do I really know anything about her?
Maybe that feeling I had of not fitting in
was the thing that drove
me to online gaming.
I guess I figured, in the virtual world,
no one knows anything about anyone.
So I dove right in, and thought
it was where I belonged.
But those two years I spent
trapped in SAO taught me something.
The difference between a real and
a virtual world is slim at best.
It's a waste of time asking
people who they really are.
All you can do is accept them
as is, and have faith in them.
Cause in the end, whoever you think
they are, that's who they really are.
When I got back to the real
world and saw Sugu's face.
I was really, truly happy.
Right then and there.
I swore I'd do whatever I could!
To try to close the gap
that had grown between us.
Over the last couple of years?
But how do I do that?
What can I do?
For Sugu.
Sugu, I'll wait for you and
Arun on the North Terrace.
How could I be so horrible to you?
And how could you be so strong?
I wish I could be as
strong as you, big brother.
I told you to hang in there.
To not give up on the one you love.
But I can't do that.
And now, I can't stop crying.
I guess this is how it is.
Leafa?
Hi. Hi.
You know, I've been
looking all over for you.
Wait, what are you doing here?
I thought the salamanders caught you.
Yeah, well, I sort of
poisoned them all and escaped.
No way.
You poisoned them? Big time.
And after I got away, I tracked to here.
Hang on.
What are you doing here alone?
Where's that Spriggan?
Oh, yeah, well...
I kind of...
said something really mean to him.
It wasn't cool, and I
shouldn't have said it.
It was...
pretty stupid of me.
Oh, never mind.
I'm just being weird.
I'm not going to be
seeing him around anymore.
Come on, let's go back to Sylvain.
Don't cry like that.
Wait!
You shouldn't be crying like that!
Sorry?
The Leafa I know is
always smiling and happy.
And I...
Well, I'd never leave you like that.
I'd stay with you always, in
here and in the real world.
I, I, uh, Leafa, I mean,
Tsuguha, I love you!
You what?
Wait, don't do that!
No, what are you doing?
Uh, are you okay?
Oh, where did I go wrong?
After everything I've said and done,
I thought all I had to do was find the
guts to confess my feelings to you.
You really are a moron, aren't you?
Even so, I could learn
a thing or two from you.
Hey.
Here I am.
Sugu, I...
Kazuto?
I want a rematch. Huh?
Let's finish what we started.
And this time, no holding back.
Now I know why he looks so composed?
Here I come!
Tch!
What are you doing?
Look, I wanted to apologize.
But I just didn't know
how to go about doing it.
So I was going to throw the duel.
You were?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry too.
I think my problem is I never really
came back to the real world after SAO.
And I can't come back until she wakes up.
In a way, the game
hasn't ended for me yet.
And I guess that's why I still haven't
figured out how I fit in at home or with you.
Not yet, anyway.
And when you do, I'll be there.
It doesn't matter how long it takes.
I'll be waiting for the day
you come back to us for real.
Until then, I'll help you in here.
So uh wait what's going on again three
players are gonna raid the world tree today?
He's player one your
player two and yours truly
makes three oh okay
wait what yui you there?
Hi, Daddy. What is it?
I need some info on the Guardians.
You learn anything?
The stats for one aren't very
high, but that's not the problem.
There's just too many of them.
As I see it, this quest was designed
to be next to impossible to finish.
So what you're saying is they all
add up to one unbeatable boss, huh?
Yes, but don't forget your
skills and XP are really high.
So maybe with a burst of speed
you can smash right through them.
Mm-hmm.
Hey, guys.
This isn't your fight.
The only way I'm gonna get
throughs with your help
But time's running out,
so we have to go now
Don't worry, I'll do whatever
I can to get you up there.
You ready?
Let's see that game face, huh?
Well, I guess I don't have a choice since
we were destined to be together forever.
Okay.
Don't talk stupid.
Oh Sorry, geez.
We're in this together!
Thanks, guys.
I mean it.
I'll draw the Guardian's attention.
While I do, stay back and heal me.
You shouldn't be in any danger, vet.
Let's go
That's awesome!
There's a lot more coming!
There's so many of them!
Now, Recon! Right!
Why are the Guardians
targeting us instead of him?
My guess is they're using
a different targeting
algorithm than any of the
other bosses in the game.
It looks like we're going to be
doing some fighting after all.
Wait!
What are you doing?
Wait a sec.
Listen, I'm not sure what's going on here,
but like, is this raid that important?
Yeah, yeah it is.
I don't think it's just a game.
Not now anyway.
Then I'm gonna help
you help that Spriggan!
Wait, Recon!
No! You idiot!
Heel!
That's enough!
Go on, get outside!
Heku Call, sval tu Call, belfa Human!
No way!
He's using a dark magic spell!
Notolegin! Garpa! Nizepa!
A self-destruct spell!
He used it even though the
penalty's worse than a normal death!
That dummy!
What was he thinking?
No!
Oh, no.
Now what?
He can't keep this up. It's impossible.
What are the sylphs doing here?
No way, they made it!
Dragons, it's the cat scene.
And they've brought the whole arc.
Hello there, I hope we're
not late. Yeah, sorry.
It took us a while to get
ready, but we're here now.
Sakuya, Alicia!
Okay, Dragoons, get ready
to toast these suckers!
Self-warriors, prepare
to engage the enemy!
Fire breath, attack!
Fenrir storm, fire at will!
Thank you!
Thank you so much for coming!
You don't have to thank us.
We can't even begin to repay
that Spriggan for all he's done.
Sakuyo's got a point, you know.
I mean,
the only reason we're here for this little
raid is because of all
the money he gave us.
Warriors!
Forward to battle!
Destroying them all! Keep going!
Sugu!
Yeah?
Watch my back, okay? You got it!
Follow their lead!
Aaaaaaaaaaah!
Aaaaaahhhh!
Ah!
Aaaaah!
Aaaaaah!
You can do it!
Go, Kazuto!
Go!
We're clearing out!
Everyone, fall back!
Keep going. Fly!
Keep flying as long as you can!
To the very end!
Damn it.
Now what do I do?
Hey, Yui!
Yes, Daddy?
Daddy, something strange is going on.
This door isn't locked by a quest flag.
It's locked by the system administrator.
What's that supposed to mean?
Restricted access!
This door was never intended
to be opened by a player!
No. Wait. That's it!
Hey, Yui, see if this'll work.
I'm transferring the code.
We're gonna teleport!
Daddy, give me your hand!
I'm not sure how to do it.
Thank you
so
much for watching.
Next time, Gilded Hero.